SAMPURNA GAUTAM

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am currently studying business and IT in Haaga-Helia with a focus on software development. I am from Nepal, but i have travelled around Europe for the past 5 years and settled down in Finland looking for professional employment. With my travel experiences I've met a variety of people and I can say with certainty that one of my strongest suits is my ability to understand and cooperate with different types of people.

Contact

0401524199

sampad789@gmail.com

Git Hub: https://github.com/sampad789

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sampurna-

gautam

Education

Bachelor in Business

Information Technology

Hagga-Helia University of Applied Sciences

2016-Present

Focus on software Engineering

Business Oriented Course

Global College Of Management 2011-2013

Work Experience CASHIER

SushiRullen | Helsinki,Finland | 2018-2019

- Stock Management
- Handling Till
- Customer Relations

Restaurant Worker

Momotoko | Helsinki ,Finland | 2019-Present

- Customer Service
- Training Staff
- Opening and Closing Duties
- Stock Management
- Handling Till

Skills

- React
- React Native
- Node is, Express.is
- Javascript
- Spring, Maven, Thymeleaf
- HTML,CSS3,BootStrap,Material UI
- Git , Databases ,Maria Db ,
 Mongodb
- Agile Methodology

Mentionables

JUNCTION 2018 PARTICIPANT

One Of the biggest hackathons in Finland

Made a React native app that supported instant Top up of balance in the phone to charge electric vehicle.

STUDENT PROJECT FOR MARKETING

CLINIC

Finnish Company's Project

Made a React app with material UI, redux, hapi and Maria DB (4 month project with 15+ students)